talent.works 2018-09-09

# Get The Job You Deserve — TalentWorks

Your privacy and trust are critically important to us. At TalentWorks we have a few fundamental principles: 

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.) 

  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights. 

  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services. 

(Because we loved it so much, we decided to use [Automattic](http://automattic.com/)'s privacy policy under the [Creative Commons Share-Alike license](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/2.5/). You should check them out. They're good people.) 

Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals: 

Predictive Talent, Inc. **("TalentWorks")** operates several websites and applications, including <https://talent.works/>. It is TalentWorks' policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites and applications. 

If you have questions about deleting or correcting your personal data please contact our [support team](mailto:hello@talent.works). 

Now, all the details— 

## Website Visitors

Like most website operators, TalentWorks collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. TalentWorks' purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how TalentWorks' visitors use its website. From time to time, TalentWorks may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. 

TalentWorks also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users logging in via Facebook. TalentWorks only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left. 

## Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to TalentWorks' websites choose to interact with TalentWorks in ways that require TalentWorks to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that TalentWorks gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for career advice at <https://talent.works/> to provide an email address, location and education history. Those who engage in transactions with TalentWorks — by signing up for a guaranteed employment contract, for example — are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, TalentWorks collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with TalentWorks. TalentWorks does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities. 

## Aggregated Statistics

TalentWorks may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, TalentWorks may monitor the most popular colleges on its <https://talent.works/> site or write a blog post about its placement percentages of its guaranteed employment contracts. TalentWorks may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, TalentWorks does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. 

## Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

TalentWorks discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on TalentWorks' behalf or to provide services available at TalentWorks' websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using TalentWorks' websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. TalentWorks will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, TalentWorks discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when TalentWorks believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of TalentWorks, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an TalentWorks website and have supplied your email address, TalentWorks may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with TalentWorks and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. TalentWorks takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information. 

## Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. TalentWorks uses cookies to help TalentWorks identify and track visitors, their usage of TalentWorks website, and their website access preferences. TalentWorks visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using TalentWorks' websites, with the drawback that certain features of TalentWorks' websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies. 

## Business Transfers

If TalentWorks, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that TalentWorks goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of TalentWorks may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy. 

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, TalentWorks may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in TalentWorks' sole discretion. TalentWorks encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
